A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Directory FA839
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Directory
1954-1981
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
FA839
2 Box(es)
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 458
Arrangement
Chronological.
Scope and Contents
The Directory contains the alphabetical listing of faculty, students, trustees, and administrative staff. Information includes the home address and telephone, the University address and telephone, spouse's first name, and secretary's name.
Bound Volumes 1954/1955 - 1977/1978 are located in the Campus Office.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Medical education; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Rockefeller University
- Directory, after 1953; 1.5 Cubic Feet
  - Fall 1959 (Box 1)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - 1961-1969 (Box 1)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - 1983 (Box 1)
  - 1986 (Box 1)
  - Changes & Updates, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Forms, A-G, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Forms, H-M, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Forms, N-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Forms, A-K, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Forms, L-Z, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)